Orientation Records UA100
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Orientation Records
1984 -- 2016
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office for Campus Life
UA100
3.5 Linear Feet 4 boxes and 1 oversize folder
1 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into four series: Orientation brochures and handouts; Ephemera and artifacts; Photographs; and Unprocessed accessions.
Custodial History
This collection was originally composed of subject oriented files, possibly collected by Russell Miller, that were not specifically associated with an office.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains artifacts, posters, photographs, publications, including brochures and handouts used at Fall Orientation for new and transfer undergraduate students.
Biographical / Historical
Responsibility for new student orientation once fell under the purview of the Orientation Committee. Currently, the Office for Campus Life takes a leadership role in the planning and implementation of New Student Orientation.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Student life; Student Affairs and Services
- Orientation brochures and handouts, 1984 -- 2016; UA100.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of brochures, calendars of events, and handouts used during fall orientations for new and transfer students.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Orientation guide, Class of 1988, 1984; UA100.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Orientation, Class of 1997, 1993; UA100.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Fall orientation calendar, Class of 1999, 1995; UA100.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Fall orientation calendar, Class of 2000, 1996; UA100.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Fall orientation calendar, Class of 2001 and transfers, 1997; UA100.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Fall orientation calendar, Class of 2002 and transfers, 1998; UA100.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Fall orientation calendar, Class of 2003 and transfers, 1999; UA100.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Orientation, Tufts 2003, Peer leader manual and handouts, 1999; UA100.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Fall orientation calendar, Class of 2005 and transfers, 2001; UA100.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Fall orientation calendar, Class of 2006 and transfers, 2002; UA100.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Fall orientation calendar, Class of 2007 and transfers, 2003; UA100.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Fall Orientation Welcome Brochure and Academic Handbook, 2009; UA100.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    Office of Campus Life
  - Fall Orientation Welcome Brochure and Academic Handbook, 2010; UA100.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Orientation '14 Experience Tufts Welcome New Students, 2014; UA100.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Orientation '15 Experience Tufts Welcome New Students, 2015; UA100.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Orientation '15 Experience Tufts Jumbo Guide, 2015; UA100.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Orientation '16 Experience Tufts Jumbo Guide, 2016; UA100.000028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Ephemera and artifacts, 1997 -- 2011; UA100.002; 0.5 Linear Feet
  This series consists of t-shirts worn by the Orientation Committee Peer Leaders during the Orientation Sessions. Also included are the books sent to incoming Freshman to provide a base for discussion, and other gift items and posters.
  - Orientation t-shirt, 1997; UA100.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Brother, I'm Dying and calendar, 2009; UA100.002.002.00002; Danticat, Edwidge (Box 2)
    This book was sent to all incoming freshman to read prior to orientation.
    Office of Campus Life; Graduate School of Arts and Sciences; Alumni Association
  - Orientation t-shirt, 2000; UA100.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Orientation t-shirt, 2002; UA100.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Experience Tufts Undergraduate Orientation poster, 2009; UA100.002.005.00001 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    poster; Office of Campus Life
  - Experience Tufts Undergraduate Orientation poster, 2010; UA100.002.005.00002 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
  - Just Ask poster, 2011; UA100.002.005.00003 (Box Large Map Case 1 Drawer 5)
    poster; Office of Campus Life; Health Services
- Photographs, 2008; UA100.003; 1 Digital Object(s)
  This series consists of photographs of incoming classes taken at Fall Orientation.
  - Class of 2012 fall orientation photograph, 2008; UA100.003.004.00001; Office of Campus Life
    Medford Campus; Students; College student orientation
- Additional accessions, UA100.000029
  - Orientation Fall 2011 materials, UA100-001 (Box data_value_missing_cf33e1e28dbae978078ec587c21bccea, Box 1)